Guide to the Alton Abraham Collection of Sun Ra 1822-2008
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Recording
  Oversize broadsides and posters, as well as a binder for the discography by Tilman Stahl, have been transferred to Series X: Subseries 3. Audio and audio-visual recordings are in Series VIII. Sample album jackets and other material related to album cover design are in Series IX. Some material in this series is duplicated in Series VI.
  - Subseries 1: Production and Promotion
    - Cosmic Rays, "Somebody's in Love," and "Bye Bye," 1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - circa 1955-1960s, Fate in a Pleasant Mood Rocket Number Nine Super-Sonic Jazz Jazz in Silhouette Other Planes of There Secrets of the Sun When Sun Comes Out The Magic City Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow When Angels Speak of Love Lady with the Golden Stockings Angels and Demons at Play Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy We Travel the Space Ways (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Jazz by Sun Ra, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Super-Sonic Jazz, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Jazz in Silhouette, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Space Loneliness, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Heliocentric World of Sun Ra, Vol. I, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Magic City, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1966, Other Planes of There Sun Ra and His Solar Arkestra Visit Planet Earth (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1967, Strange Strings The Magic City Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow When Angels Speak of Love The Nubians Plutonia ‘We Travel the Space Ways' Interstellar Low Ways ‘Cosmic Tone for Mental Therapy' (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Space is the Place, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Astro Black, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Lanquidity, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Other Side of the Sun, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - John Cage Meets Sun Ra, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1995, Love in Outer Space Pleiades Friendly Galaxy Live at the Hackney Empire A Quiet Place in the Universe (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Undated, When Sun Comes Out, Vol. I When Sun Comes Out, Vol. II When Sun Comes Out, Vol. III Super-Sonic Jazz Jazz in Silhouette Music from Tomorrow's World Flights over Jupiter Rocket to Outer Space Planet Earth Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy Neptunal Horizons (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Undated, The Magic City Space is the Place Discipline 27-11 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Undated, "Baritone Retinue" "Soul Vibrations" "Taking a Chance" "Continuation" (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Undated, "Blues at Midnight" "Sunology" "Soft Talk" (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Discographies
    - Alton Abraham, El Saturn Records discographies, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Tilman Stahl, "Sun Ra Materialen/Sun Ra Material," discography, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Discographies, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Jean Buzelin and Alain-René Hardy, "Disco Sun Ra/1," discography, 1953-1970, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "Sun Ra Discography," Robert L. Campbell, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
- Series IV: Music Manuscripts
  This series contains manuscripts of Sun Ra's music writing. Also included are music manuscripts prepared by others, and copies of original manuscripts. There are arrangements, compositions, sketches, lyrics, notes and fragmentary music notations. Peripheral material of Sun Ra and Alton Abraham, such as correspondence and notes, is also retained with the manuscripts, though it is not always related. Most manuscripts are undated, but generally range from the 1960s-1980s.
  This series is organized into two subseries:
  Subseries 1: Sun Ra Manuscripts, contains Sun Ra's manuscripts of his own music, as well as his arrangements of jazz standards. There are holograph manuscripts as well as copies that Sun Ra used to document copyright. Also included are untitled and fragmentary works, and a notebook containing a variety of Sun Ra's music writings.
  Subseries 2: Manuscripts by Others, includes compositions by Alton Abraham, Walter Dunn, Ruth Lewis, Faith McBride, and unidentified composers. Some manuscripts may represent versions of Sun Ra's works that were transcribed by others, or works on which Sun Ra collaborated with others. Included are later manuscripts of songs recorded in the late 1950s by the Chicago R&B performer Yochanan. Materials are organized by size.
  Manuscripts consisting primarily of lyrics and other verse writings are in Series V.
  - Subseries 1: Sun Ra Manuscripts
    - "21st Century," (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "Barbizon" (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "City in the Clouds" (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Coordination" (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Cosmos-Sun-Day" (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "Discipline #1" (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Discipline 99" (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Hi Spook" (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - "I'm Gonna Unmask the Batman" (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Loco" (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - "Love in Outer Space" (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Opus 5" (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Opus Springtime" (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Saturn" (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Space Loneliness" (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Star Time" (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "Who in the World Do You Love?" (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Wrappin' It Up" (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Yeah Man!" (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Manuscripts, "Astro-Black" "Astro-Black Mythology" "Cosmo-Celebration" (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, "Can You Take It?" "Keep Smilin'" "New Horizons" "Stratosphere" (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, "Door of the Cosmos" "I Kiss Your Hand Madam" "Travel the Spaceways" (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, "Akasoinying" "D3" "Deep Purple" "Intragalactic Thing" "Pan Astro" "Sunology" "TNR 1980#2" (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, "January 23, 1971" "March 16, 1985" (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Untitled manuscripts (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "83 Comet" (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Astro Black" [Item on loan through April 2024. Please see staff for more information.] (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Hidden Spheres" [Item on loan through April 2024. Please see staff for more information.] (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, "Discipline 33" "Sea of Sounds" "Space is the Place" (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "The Cosmo-Fire" (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Rocket Number Nine" (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Magic City" [Item on loan through April 2024. Please see staff for more information.] (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Notebook (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Atlantis" (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - "True love is never lost..." (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Frisco Fog" (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Let's Go Slumming" (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Running a Temperature" (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "At Sundown" (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "Blue Lou" (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Can this Be Love?" (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Dream of You" (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Four or Five Times" (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Frisco Fog" (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Gone with the Wind" (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "I'll Get By" (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - "I'll Never Be the Same" (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "I'll String Along with You" (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "Little John" (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Might Lak' a Rose" (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - "Queer Notions" (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "Slippery Horn" (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - "Yard Dog Mazurka" (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Manuscripts, "Chicago Daze" "Le Heimt Noel" (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts, "Chloe" "What Is this Thing Called Swing?" (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Manuscripts, "Diane" "Rugcutters Stomp" (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Manuscripts, "Bye Bye Blackbird" "Keep Smiling" "Say It Isn't So" (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Manuscripts, "Happy as the Day Is Long" "That Old Feeling" (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Manuscripts, "Body and Soul" "Lime House Blues" "Linger Awhile" "Willow Weep for Me" (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Manuscripts, "Alone Together" "My Funny Valentine" "Rainbowville" (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Fakebook and sheet music fragments (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 2: Manuscripts by Others
    - Manuscripts, "Domesticated Love" "Get Your Shoes on for Savannah" "Gonna Fall in Love with You" "Lonely Me" "No Kind of Love Have I" "Old Dreams, Sad Dreams" "Sad and Lonely "Summer Job" "Umbally-Yah!" (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, "Get Your Shoes on for Savannah" "Lonely Me" "Summer Job" "Um Bali-Bali" (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, "Domesticated Love" "Every Hour" "Get Your Shoes on for Savannah" "Gonna Fall in Love with You" "Muck Muck (Maat Maat)" "Old Dreams, Sad Dreams" "Sad and Lonely" "Summer Job" "Umbally-Yah!" (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, "Hot Skillet Mama" "Muck Muck (Maat Maat)" (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Two of a Kind" (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "From sunset to darkness..." (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Music notebook (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified works (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Recorder music (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series V: Verse, Prose and Notes
  This series contains manuscripts, proofs, broadsides, pamphlets, notebooks and books by Sun Ra. It also includes notes, fragmentary works, and a small number of works by Alton Abraham and unidentified writers. Most items are undated, but generally span the 1950s-1980s. Correspondence of Sun Ra is retained with many of his writings. This series is organized alphabetically by title, subject or format.
  One distinctive group of material is a collection of notebooks kept by Sun Ra and Alton Abraham. These contain a variety of content such as numerological figures, sketches, notes, and drafts of verse and prose. This series also contains several files related to The Immeasurable Equation, two volumes of Sun Ra's verse: This material includes manuscripts, proofs, sample copies and cover stock. There are other verse compilations including the unpublished The Magic Lie. Also of note are circa 1950s-1960s typescripts and broadsides in which Sun Ra articulated his beliefs during a formative part of his career. An unusual item is Sun Ra's application to an arts program operated by the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA).
  Oversize proof sheets of pages of the Immeasurable Equation have been transferred to Series X: Subseries 4. Written music, including music with lyrics, is in Series IV.
  - "Comments and Poetry by Sun Ra," circa 1960s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "The Differences," 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Egyptian alphabet, circa 1980s (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Everyday events bear witness..." undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Flight to Mars," undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Gather together our dispersion..." undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "I do not remember being born..." undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Immeasurable Equation, circa 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 7-10)
  - The Immeasurable Equation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11-18)
  - The Immeasurable Equation, 1972, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - The Immeasurable Equation, Extensions Out: The Immeasurable Equation, volume 2, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
  - "In the beginning..." circa 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Jazz in Silhouette," circa 1958-1960s (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - "Jazz in Silhouette," circa 1958-1960s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "Jesus Gave You a Peace of His Mind," undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Jesus Said, 'Let the Negro Bury the Negro'," undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Magic Lie, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Music: The Space Language," undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Letterhead, Sun Ra, with handwritten notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NASA program application, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "The Neglected Plane of Wisdom," circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 9-13)
  - Notebook, circa 1963-1965 (Box 14)
  - Writings and sketches transferred from notebook, circa 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - "Oh Terrible Knower (Noah)," circa 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "Safari," undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Solomon," undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Statements by Sun Ra, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Sun Ra Live at the Black Music Conference 4/73 at Amherst College," circa 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "Think a Prayer," 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Thought Flash," "Tone Pictures," undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "The Tower of Babel," undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "A Treatise on Rebirth," undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Prose and verse, circa 1950s, "Satan Is the God Of the Spooks, Negroes Are the Children of The Devil" "Negroes Are Not Men" "The Negro Is a Burden to the White Man!" "Message to the Spook" "Lucifer Means Light Bearer" "Spo De O De...Hoc Way..." "The Great Whore" "Job in the Land of Uz Means Negroes in the Land of Us (U.S.)" "There's a Nigger in the Woodpile" "Basic Truths" "Logic" "Humpty Dumpty" "United States at the Crossroads" "The Reach for a Better World: Light for the Gentiles" "What Must Negroes Do to Be Saved?" "Language of the Gods" "The True Way to Life" "The Light Isg/Let there Be Light!" "Days of Vengeance!" "Mes is Mesh..." "The Way of the Cross" "There Are Two Ethiopias" "The God of Israel" "The Stumbling Block" "I Don't Give a Hoot" "Why Don't You Turn Again?" "Big Brother Left You Holding the Bag!" "Moms & Pops" "The Poor Little Rich One: The Princes of this World" "Neptune is Rex...The Ruler with the Iron Fork" "Johnny One Note" "A Nigger is a Mess/Jeremiah 19" "Nam-Myoho-Renge-Kyo (The Hokekyo and the Daimoku)" "Genesis 3:22..." "Egypt..." "The Truth about Jesus" "I Have Set Before You Life and Death -- Choose Life" "Solution to the Negro Problem" "Wake Up! Wake Up! Wake Up!" "The Bible Was Not Written for Negroes!" "The End" (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Verse collection, undated, Index "The Sound Meaning" "The Spontaneous Love" "Different" "To Some Destination" "The Lightning Realities" "Thoth" "The Farther" "The Glory of Shame" "Invisibility" "Hands" "Twin Vibrations" "To whom do I speak today?" "Concerning that Which Is Called Life and Death" (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Verse and prose collection, undated, "The Crate Create" "Sun-day" "The Invisible Giants" "When You Meet a Man" "The Sun Is There!" "The Spontaneous Love" "The Order of the Ardor" "To Outer Unseen Worlds" "The earth man and the air/spirit man..." "The Enwrit" "Equality:parallelism" "I/We" "Ignorance" "The Tone of Abstract Love" "Confrontations" "The Melody of the Air" "The Thick Darkness" "Of the Myth" "Different" "Parallels" "Figure" "The Curse-Blueprint" "For Being" "Fabricate" "Essence/Energy" "The Outer Darkness" "The No Point" "Angelic Brothers" "The Name Sound" "I Have Forgotten" "After That" "Words" (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Verse, undated, "Brothers of the Sun" "The Tradition Creator" "The Outer Beyond" "The Inned Inning" "I Have Forgotten" "The Irresistible Thought" "If I Told You" "The Skilled Way" "Tomorrow's Vibrations" "The Confusion of Words" "The Damning" "Prophecy" "Alter Is" "The Pure Sound" "The Spiral Way" "The Equal and the Opposite" "Of Notness" "The Garden of Eatened" "Invisibility" "Of the Day that Died" "The Brass Herald" "Preface" "Love and Hate" "The Shadow of the Fire" "Borders of Nowhere" "The Soul Dealer" "Unremembered Dreams" "Truth:Bad:Good" "Victory Dual" "The Endless Universe" "The Place of Searching I" "On Solar Planes" "The Differences" "The Unknown State" "Of the Cosmic-Blueprints" "Wisdom-Ignorance" "We Hold this Myth to Be Potential" "Memory Says" "Some Tomorrow" "The Potential" "The Curtain Call" "The Spontaneous Love" "Other Planes of There" "The Flesh" "By Golly!" "Thing in Itself" "Fragments of the Alter-Future" "The Ridiculous I" "To Some Destination" "Never is the Future" "Word World" "Nothing Is" "Energies" "The Bound Eternity" "The Outer Darkness" "The Garden of Eden" "The Fire and the Dry Weeds" "The Wasters" "Would I For All that Were" "Be - Earthed" "The Glory of Shame" "On the Bypass" "Self Radiation" "Beyond the Truths" "Yon Man" "On the Edge of the Thin Between" "The Endless Universe" "The No Point" "Birds without Wings" "Detour" "Whereness" "The Endless Realm" "Intergalactic Master" "Cosmos Evolution" "The Cosmic-Myth" "The Outer Bridge" "Planes of Nature" "Twice Told" (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Verse, undated, "Cosmic Equation" "The Narrow Way" "Of the Realm of Vision" "Children" "Though Fragments" "According to Nature's Law" "They're Peepin' In" (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Verse, undated, "Of Light Things" "Spirals" "The On Rays" "Someone Else and Others" "The Limited Mind" (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Business Records
  This series contains records of the business operations of Saturn Records and other endeavors managed by Alton Abraham in collaboration with Sun Ra and others. The bulk of this material was kept by Alton Abraham, though he may have collected some items from Sun Ra, John Gilmore and others.
  Alton Abraham's businesses operated under many different names and iterations. Business names are given as documented on items. Files are organized chronologically, with undated material at the end of the series. Materials date from 1939-1998, but relate mainly to business activities from the late 1950s through the mid-1990s. In addition to material related to the management of Sun Ra and members of the Arkestra, this series also documents Abraham's involvement with other performers and work as a dealer in occult books.
  Material in this series includes legal agreements on matters such as recording, performance, record distribution and promotion; business forms and stationery; financial records, such as statements, invoices, reports, and receipts; ephemera, such as catalogs, broadsides, handbills, pamphlets, brochures and other promotional material; and instructional books and pamphlets related to music recording and production. General correspondence includes business mail, promotional material, customer orders and fan mail. Also included are notebooks kept by Alton Abraham: these contain a variety of content, including contact lists; draft promotional copy; notes on recordings and performances; and notes on personal matters.
  Oversize financial records, correspondence, publicity material, notes and blank legal forms have been transferred to Series X: Subseries 5. Additional materials related to Abraham's hobbies and entrepreneurial interests are in Series VII. Additional documents of Sun Ra performances and recordings are in Series II and III.
  - F.H Goldsmith and V.G. Geisel, Techniques of Recording: A Practical Hand-Book on Recording, monograph, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Leroy Hughbanks, You Can Make Records, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Saturn Records, "New Release Announcement: 'Super-Sonic Jazz' by Sun Ra and his Arkestra," broadsides, circa 1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Financial records, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Down Beat Promotions for Profit," portfolio, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, 1956-1966 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Financial records, 1956-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Record distribution, draft agreement, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Account book, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Wurlitzer organs, promotional material, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Notebook, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Central Show Printing Company, brochure, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Music performance trust funds, forms and reports, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Music recording and production, correspondence, circa 1959-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, 1950s (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Saturn Records, promotional correspondence and ephemera, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Stereo and recording equipment, promotional material, circa 1950s- 1960s (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Saturn Records, draft recording contracts, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Record distribution, correspondence, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fletcher Myatt, correspondence, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Saturn Records, sample contracts and promotional material, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Notes, circa 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Notebooks, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - General correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Come Back, Africa screening at Doc Films, University of Chicago, correspondence, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - McLin Ensemble, program, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Down Beat Promotions for Profit," portfolio, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Saturn Records, "From the World of Saturn Records," catalogs, circa 1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Down Beat magazines, 1963-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ruth Lewis, resume and photograph, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Playboy Theater, program, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Financial ledger, 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Jazz by Sun Ra," advertisement reprint, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - General correspondence, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 17-19)
  - Notes, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - El Saturn Records, "Strange Strings," catalog, circa 1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - Walter Thiers, correspondence, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Recording contract forms and notes, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Jazz magazine, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Record mailing list, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - John Taggart, correspondence, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Record distributors catalogs, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - El Saturn Records, catalogs, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Copyright forms, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Saturn "II" Research, Dimpna B. Clarin, correspondence and promotional material, circa 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - LZMC Inc., promotional correspondence, circa 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - LZMC Inc., promotional photographs, circa 1967-1968, Lu Elliott Woody Guenther and the Cheaters Lacey James Ruby and the Romantics George Smith (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - General correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Atra Productions, announcement and letterhead, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hellas Café, handbill, circa 1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Atra Productions, Lacy Gibson, promotional material, circa 1968 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Lena McLin, promotional material, circa 1968 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Saturn Research Foundation, book catalogs and letterhead, circa 1968 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Saturn Research Foundation, book catalogs and letterhead, circa 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Playboy marketing portfolio, circa 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Filming rights agreement drafts and correspondence, circa 1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Tam Fiofori, correspondence, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Billy Mitchell (Mitchell W. Boisseau) and Duo Records, recording agreement, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Music performance trust funds, agreements, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Saturn Records Research, sales representative solicitations, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Financial records, circa 1960s (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - General correspondence, circa 1960s (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Notebook, circa 1960s (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Saturn's Fan Club," postcards, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - El Saturn Research, invoice pads, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - El Saturn Records, letterhead, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Enterplanetary Koncepts, legal forms, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Saturn Research Foundation, book catalogs, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Saturn Records Research, letterhead, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - El Saturn Research, invoice forms, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - El Saturn Records, "Good News From...El Saturn Records," postcards, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Legal forms, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Sonny's Stereo Village, catalogs, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Atra Productions, broadside, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Saturn Records Research, Maeght Foundation recording agreement, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)